voobys.com 2016-03-13

# Privacy voobys.com

Privacy

At voobys, we respect the privacy of the users of our website and services and are committed to protecting it. We have created this policy to demonstrate our commitment to you and to help you understand it. By visiting the voobys website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers voobys's treatment of personal information that voobys gathers when you are on the voobys website and when you use voobys services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that voobys does not own or control, or to individuals that voobys does not employ or manage. 

Information Collected by voobys 

we may collect personal information, including email addresses and users interests, when individuals register to use the voobys! website and services, post a link to the voobys website or submit questions, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users' IP addresses and information regarding our users' use of our website and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. Unless required by law, we will not share our users' personal information, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and usage information, except with their consent or in aggregate or anonymous form, with third parties. In order to offer and provide optimized and personalized services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive. 

E-mail Communications

voobys is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. voobys may send out e-mails with voobys-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. You may also receive notification e-mails from voobys, which inform you of actions (e.g. friend requests) that have been performed on the site. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please visit the Email Preferences section of your User Profile and/or follow the instructions contained in the unwanted e-mail message. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us. 

Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. voobys cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is. The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of voobys's coolest features. Some of our business partners, like our advertisers, may use cookies on our website. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies. 

Keeping Information Secure

Your voobys account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. 

Children Under 18 Years of Age

You must be 13 years and older to register to use the voobys website. As a result, voobys does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that voobys has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents' permission before using voobys or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy

voobys may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the voobys website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. 

Google Analytics & Adwords Disclaimer 

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. Furthermore, this website uses AdWords' free conversion tracking feature. 

Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of august 1, 2012
